life I say welcome brothers and sisters
to another Wednesday question and answer
will we open up with the T Commandments
that God commanded the whole world to
keep brother tanzel and God spake all
these words saying I am the Lord thy God
which have brought thee out of the land
of Egypt out of the house of bondage
thou shall have no other gods before me
thou sh not make it to the any Graven
image or any likeness of anything that
is in heaven the b or that is in the
earth beneath what that is in the water
under the Earth thou shall not bow down
thyself to them nor serve them why the
Lord thy God I'm a jealous God visiting
the iniquities of the fathers upon the
children unto the third and fourth
generation of them that hate me and
showing Mercy unto thousands of them
that love me and keep my Commandments
thou shall not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain for the Lord will not
hold him Guiltless that take of his name
in vain remember the Sabbath day to keep
it holy six days shall thou labor and do
all thy work but the seven day is the
Sabbath of the Lord thy God in it thou
shall not do any work thou nor thy son
nor thy daughter thy man servant nor thy
maid servant nor thy cattle nor thy
stranger that is within thy gates for in
six days the Lord made Heaven and Earth
the sea and all that in them is and
resteth the seventh day wherefore the
Lord blessed the Sabbath day and
hollowed it under thy father and thy
mother that th days may be long upon the
land which the Lord thy God give thee
thou shall not kill thou shall not
commit adultery thou shall not steal
thou not bear false witness against thy
neighbor thou not cover thy neighbor's
house thou not cover thy neighbor's wife
nor his man's servant nor his May
servant nor his Ox nor his ass nor
anything that is thy neighbors we read
Exodus 21-17 and may the Lord have a
blessing to the reading of his words in
Jesus name we pray amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answer
it according to the King James Bible and
if we cannot find the answer we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time keep in mind that
all B questions will not be answered and
all long scripture questions will not be
answered for time sake but we may be
able to point you in the direction of a
CD or dvd that you can purchase by
calling office so please be as direct as
possible with your questions
so we can be as direct as possible with
our answers out of the King James Bible
no other Bibles will be acknowledged on
this program also keep in mind that this
is a live stream and you may begin to
send in your questions at this time even
questions that pertain to everlasting
life we're just asking that you keep
your questions to a two scripture
maximum let me introduce to you the
family that's on the panel this evening
brother Dre good evening brother Julius
good evening to
everybody brother Jerome Grace and peace
Brother tanzel good evening sister
Deborah good
evening and we have sister Casey with us
as well as the guest caller and I'm
brother Cornell what is our first
question of the
evening yes uh there are several held
over questions that will be answered
first
before getting into tonight's Q&A dot
ask when the Fallen Angels fell to Earth
were they still in spirit form or human
and did they receive the Breath of
Life all right so when the Angels fell
to Earth were they still in spirit form
and asking about that they receive the
Breath of Life brother Jerome share some
light well all of the angel were created
uh spirit beings um and they going to
remain Spirit beings they're not going
to change into humans and uh spirit
beings they don't need to breathe any
air humans need to breathe air to live
okay but let's go to Hebrews the first
chapter and and read verse 6 and 7 10
Hebrews chapter 1 read verse 6 and 7 you
get it go ahead and read
and again when he bringeth in the first
begotten unto the world he said let all
the angel of God worship Him and of the
angels He said who make of his angels
spirits and his ministers a flame of
fire okay so you say he maketh his
angels spirits and if they had been
changed into
humans then uh they wouldn't have been
able to make this statement that we
going to read in this Matthews 8
thousands of years later about being uh
punished before they time okay so let's
just go read that Matthews 8 read verse
28-32 you know uh human beings can't
live beyond uh a thousand years so if
they had been hum they' have died long
before making these statements we about
to read Matthew 8: 28-32
when you get it go ahead and when he was
come to the other side into the country
of the GG SCS there met him two
possessed with Devils coming out of the
Tomb exceeding Fierce so that no man
might pass by that
way and behold they cried out saying
what have we to do with thee Jesus thou
Son of God are Thou come hither to
torment us before the time go ahead and
there was a good way off from them and
heard uh a herd of many swine feeding so
the Devils besought him saying if thou
cast us out suffer us to go away into
the herd of
swine and he said unto them well go and
when they were come out they went into
the herd of swine and behold the whole
herd of swine ran violently down the
Steep Place into the sea and perish in
the waters yeah so them them statements
were making thousands of
years after they were cast out of uh
heaven so no they Spirit BS and they
gonna always be Spirit BS that's all I
got
on all right thank you for that brother
hope that answered that question as we
move on to our next Moving On noris Tap
says why do you think that Jesus when
cursing the serpent had it written that
he be cursed above all the beasts of the
field shouldn't he have been if the
serpent was an angel and they give
Genesis 3
verse4 all right so they give Genesis
three and verse 14 and we're going to
ask the guest caller to share some light
from
there I'm going share some real light on
this you just wait until Jesus come and
you ask
him and you implying that whatever Jesus
did he made an
error I tell you something I don't have
that kind of n so this question here you
can say for Jesus that's all I have to
say all right we're gonna leave it right
there as we continue to move on to our
next one yes amazing as why does
Revelations say the churches are in Asia
who are these churches
today all right Revelation does mention
the churches in Asia but who are these
churches today brother Julius let's go
to Revelation chapter
1 and Asia is Asia Minor which is today
modern day turkey and they are
considered holy sites according to the
the Turkish
government Revelation chapter
1 and pick it up at verse four
10z Revelation 1 and verse four go
ahead John to the seven churches which
are in Asia great be unto you and peace
from him which is and which was and
which is to come and from the seven
spirits which are before his throne so
now these seven churches was assigned
seven angels and the angels would give
messages to the churches which is the
what we call the churches in Asia Min
and under the New Testament in the Roman
province because they were still Rome
still ruled the whole Known World at
that time and still now so what happened
was the Lord sent uh had John write
these uh uh write the Book of Revelation
on the island of pmos to the seven
churches and it look each each one of
them has an angel assigned to it pick it
up at verse n because this is a prophecy
involved in here not just it's a a
prophecy of the church
then and of the seven churches all the
way up to even now go ahead I John who
also am your brother and companion
tribulation and in the kingdom and
patience of Jesus Christ was in the
hours that is called Patmos for the word
of God and for the testimony of Jesus
Christ and that's what John was on the
island of Patmos for for the testimony
of Jesus Christ and for the word of God
verse 10 please I was in the spirit on
the Lord's day and heard behind me a
great voice as of a
trumpet saying I am Alpha and o Omega
the first and the last and what thou See
Is Right In book and send it unto the
seven churches which are in Asia unto
Ephesus and unto Smurda and unto
pergamos and unto thara and unto Sardis
and unto Philadelphia and into l doia so
now that that's the each Church received
an angel that give the message to the
people regarding uh and the whole theme
of each one of those we could read the
whole story to the seven churches the
bottom line is the message to them was
to keep the faith and endure to the end
from that point all the way to this
point that's all I got for right
now keep the faith endure it to the end
and keep the faith each
Church all right thank you for that hope
that answered their question as we move
on to our next moving on noris tape says
so there are three trees of Life the
fruit tree in Revelations 22 and Jesus
and the father I did want to know where
we can read it
exactly also I was thinking so if Jesus
was the tree of life back in the garden
was he concerned about Adam putting
forth his hand to touch him after he had
eaten from the Tree of knowledge and uh
Genesis 3 verse 22 is
given all right Genesis 3 and 22 okay
guess carer can you share some light on
that
question a but two trees of life that's
the father and the son and these other
trees was trees that grew out the Dr and
the only way they could have a give any
kind of life because the Lord created
them to do so like he did with medicine
but let's look at let's and and let's
look at revelation 22 and2 read that
real
quick go
ahead in the midst of the streets of it
and on either side of the river was
there the Tree of Life which bear 12
manner of fruits and yielded up fruits
every month and the leaves of the tree
were for the healing of the Nations
okay now this is in the father's Kingdom
so what is this this is just like the
the uh time when Israel had that b of
manner that from Heaven this is just a
relic of the time when the Ezekiel uh
spoke about doing Jesus Kingdom let's go
into Ezekiel the 47th chapter and read
verse
12 read when you get there
and by the river upon the bank thereof
on the side and On th side shall grow
all trees for meat whose leaves shall
not fade neither shall the fruits
thereof be consumed it shall bring forth
new fruit according to his month because
their Waters they issue out of the
sanctuary and the fruits thereof shall
be for meat and the leaf thereof for
medicine now this is the same one that
was in now that Revelation spoke this is
the same trees but they don't need them
in
Revelation uh uh uh uh 22nd chapter is
because there ain't no more death let's
go to Revelation 21st chapter and read
verses 1 through
4 Revelation uh 1 chapter
1-4 uhuh Revelation 21
of Revelation
21 New Jerusalem and I saw a new Heaven
and a new Earth for the first Heaven and
the first Earth were passed away and
there was no more sea and I John saw the
holy city New Jerusalem coming down from
God out of Heaven prepared as a bride
adorned for her
husband
uh and I heard a great voice out of
Heaven saying behold the Tabernacle of
God is with men and he will dwell with
them and they shall be his people and
God himself shall be with them and be
their
God and God shall wipe away all tears
from their eyes and there shall be no
more death neither sorrow nor cry
neither shall there be any more pain for
the former things are passed
away so now when nobody can die you
don't need a tree with healing leaves
you don't need a tree that produ that
called a tree of life that's why it was
because when Jesus came him here you
don't have to have no doctor you can eat
of the fruit for food and when you get
sick you can eat of the Le but that
those are talking about Flesh and Blood
people but here in this 21st chapter of
Revelation and in 22nd chapter of
Revelation everybody are Immortal and
there is no more death let go you show
you because Jesus turned terminated that
let's go into 1 Corinthians 15th chapter
and read verse 21- 26 you can read it
quickly for Since By Man Came Death by
man came also the resurrection of the
Dead for as an Adam all died even so in
Christ shall all be made alive but every
man in his own order Christ the first
fruits afterwards they that are Christ
at his coming then cometh the end when
he shall have delivered up the kingdom
of God e in the father when he shall put
down all Rule and all authority and
power for he must reain till he have put
all enemies under his feet The Last
Enemy that shall be destroyed is
death okay so there ain't no more
death why because Jesus
terminated so these trees were just
something Jesus that that we use like
right now you got certain medicine you
can use when you're sick it will keep
you from dying the Lord just had trees
where you wouldn't eat no doctor so they
ain't but two Tree of Life those the one
that can give life that's the father and
the
son and at that time the 22nd chapter of
Revelation during the father's Kingdom
there is no more death so who need and
no more sickness so we need a tree of
life it is merely a relic to show what
used to be yeah I where this other one
he's talking about touching God didn't
want Adam to touch him let's go Genesis
the 3rd Chapter and read verse 22 see
what it
said and the Lord God said behold the
man has become as one of us to know good
and evil and now let he put forth his
hand and take also of the tree of life
and eat and live
forever now that have nothing to do with
a physical touching that have something
to do with
conversation just like he had a
conversation with Satan and dance was
brought in now the Lord said hey I don't
want him to to have no conversation to
hear us
talking because uh I don't because if he
uh because he can learn how to live
forever so it ain't got nothing to do to
church it got something to do with
conversation go and read St John
663 St John 663
it is the spirit that Quicken the flesh
profited nothing the words that I speak
unto you they are spirit and they are
life so when the Lord put Adam out of
the garden he didn't want him to hang
around and listen to Jesus which was
talking to the
father and learn how to live forever it
got nothing to do with touching him
that's why he said flesh prophet nothing
is the words that I speak unto you they
are spirit and they are life that's
right so he put him out to hear the
conversation and learn how to live
forever because he had been tainted by
Satan that's all I have to say all right
hope that answered your question there
as we continue to move
on moving on I chuck woo arar ask for
you to explain Matthew
24: 40-4
all right explanation on that Matthew 24
40-42 brother Jerome what you
got let's go to that Matthews um brother
tanzel Matthews 24 verse 40- 42 when you
get it go ahead and read then shall two
be in the field the one shall be taken
and the other left two women shall be
grinding at the meal the one shall be
taken and the other left
watch therefore but ye know not what
hour your lord do
come okay now we going to go to acts the
second chapter so we can take a look and
understand what this taken
mean in this chapter right here okay
let's go to acts the 2
chapter and read verse 9-1 it give you
an example what taken mean in this
Matthews 24 the verses that you gave
you said Acts 2 Acts 2 verse
9-1 um acts one I'm
sorry you saw that acts
one thank you brother tanel acts
one go ahead read it when you get
it until the day in which he was taken
up after that he through the Holy Ghost
have given Commandments unto the
apostles whom he had
chosen to whom also he showed himself
alive after his Passion by many
infallible proof being seen of them 40
days and speaking of the things
pertaining the kingdom of God and being
assembled together with them commanded
them that they should not depart from
Jerusalem but wait for the promise of
the Father which said he ye have heard
of me for John truly baptized with water
but ye shall be baptized with the Holy
Ghost not many days hence so you want
you I want
acts one and I'm appreciate you
correcting me on that acts one but I
want verse 9 through 11 okay part the
body and when he had spoken these things
while they be beheld he was taken up and
the cloud received him out of their
sight yeah and while they looked
steadfastly toward Heaven as he went up
behold two men stood by them in white
apparel
which also said ye men of Galilee why
stand ye gazing up into heaven this same
Jesus who was taken up from you into
heaven so so come in like man as ye have
seen him go up into heaven yeah and so
in that Matthews 24 when he said the uh
the one was taken the other left he
talking about he gonna be taken up you
know like you read in Thessalonians so
everybody in Thessalonians that's going
to be the first resurrection they're
going to be taken up to meet the Lord in
the clouds that's what the taken mean
okay so let's go to that Thessalonians 1
Thessalonians chapter 4 and read verse
16 and
17 for the Lord himself shall descend
from heaven with a shout with the voice
of the Archangel and with the Trump of
God and the dead in Christ shall rise
first
then we which are alive and remain shall
be caught up together with them in the
clouds to meet the Lord in the air and
so shall we ever be with the Lord yeah
and the same thing gonna happen with the
two witnesses they gonna be taken up to
meet the Lord in the clouds you know we
a we ain't going to go there but you can
read that in uh Revelations the 11th
chapter verse 11 through 12 you know um
that's all I got on that you know the
ones that's left everybody that don't
make that first resurrection they going
to be left on this Earth they ain't
going to rise up or be taken nowhere
they going to be left standing on this
Earth no matter where they are on this
Earth no matter what they doing at the
time they'll be left standing on this
Earth that's right that's all I got on
there all right thank you for that
brother and we don't want nobody to be
deceived that is not the Rapture not
even written in Bible is no it wasn't
there no that's where they get that
Rapture from so brother Jerome just
shared some light on what's going to
actually take place so you can delete
Rapture out of your belief all right
hope that answered your question as we
move on to our
next moving on fire F says in Exodus 20
vers 8 through 11 it says honor the
Sabbath and keep it holy what can we do
to honor can we go outside for a walk
and enjoy being
outside all right for this Mighty God on
the Sabbath day brother Dre what you say
let's go to that Exodus uh 20 and read
verses 8
to1 Exodus 20
8-1 read it 10 when you get it remember
the Sabbath day to keep it holy six days
shall thou lab and do all thy work but
the seventh day is the Sabbath of the
Lord thy God in it thou shall not do any
work thou nor thy son nor thy daughter
thy man servant nor thy maid servant nor
thy cattle nor thy stranger that is
within thy gates for in six days the
Lord made Heaven and Earth the seat and
all that in them is and rested the seven
day wherefore the Lord blessed the
Sabbath day and hollowed it that's how
we Hollow it by keeping it but let's go
to uh Isaiah 58 and read verse 13 Isaiah
58 and
13 what are some of the things that we
can do to honor and can we go walking on
that day you know if if you going
walking are you
exercised are you going walking to do a
swift walk and
exercise what is the meaning behind it
if if it's just to walk I can't find
nothing in the scripture about that but
in terms of keeping the Sabbath day
holy here's what we do Isaiah 58 verse3
go ahead and read it brother thou turn
away thy foot from the Sabbath from
doing thy pleasure on my holy day and
call the Sabbath of delight the holy of
the Lord honorable and shall honor him
not doing thy own ways nor finding th
own pleasure nor speaking thy own words
then shall thou Delight thyself in the
Lord and I will cause thee to ride upon
the high places of the earth and feed
thee with the inheritance of Jacob thy
father for the mouth of the Lord hath
spoken it this is straight from the
mouth of the Lord a blessing if you
honor the Sabbath day not doing your own
pleasure or finding your own ways or
speaking your own words
but walking in the Commandments of god
let's go to one other place let's go to
Isaiah 56 bag up to 56 and read verse
two that's it brother 56 and two go
ahead blessed the man that doeth this
and the son of man that layth hold on it
that keepeth the Sabbath from polluting
it and keepeth his hand from doing any
evil so don't do any evil on the Sabbath
day that's how you can honor the Sabbath
day not pollute the Sabbath day by doing
things that are against it so uh I hope
that that helps that's it that's what I
got for
it sir brother Dre that day is supposed
to be highly respected by every man
woman and child isn't it
absolutely yes sir thank you for that
explanation all right sister Deborah
time check as we keep moving
yes the time is
7:58 CC sent by Christ says if my
siblings is living in
fornication shouldn't I tell them to
stop
immediately and how often should I be on
them about it I don't want to turn
anyone from the word but I know time is
short all right guess caller what you
got for that situation
well you have you have to warn them at
least one
time and let them know about uh the
consequences of it and if they'll let
you you can read the scripture to them 1
Corinthians 7
and9 First Corinthians
7 and
N but if they cannot contain let them
marry for it is buried to marry than the
burn now you can tell them that and say
look you should read this if you can't
uh uh uh contain yourself or sustain it
from have having sex then get to your
spouse because if you don't you're going
to burn in Fire and they said it's
better to marry than to burn if they
don't want to hear it then you don't
deal with them no more leave them alone
because what's going to happen is and
the Lord told you not to cast your
prayer before swin because going to
trample your Pearl and then they will
turn around and ren you in other words
they're going to start hating you so you
obligated to tell them one time that
this is against the word of God and the
consequences is going to the lake of
fire and if they don't take heed to it
you've done yours leave them
alone that's all I got to say all
right hope that answers your question as
we can continue to move
on yes moving on uh brother Cornell if
my
heart if it's my heart's desire to be
baptized why do I have to be
circumcised because that is the order of
things that's the way that the Lord has
set it up and it sounds like it go ahead
let me ask this all right because
because people act like
that uh uh
uh that Paul is greater than Jesus CU he
going to take you second Corinthians the
3 chapter right all
right so let's go and read
that and that's the 12 down at verse 12
we're going to read some of
that second Corinthians 3 And1
right we going we goingon to read about
18 read quickly because I got I got some
scripture I want to put on this because
I am tired of people coming trying to
let the writing of Paul override God's
right go read it when you get
there seeing then that we have such hope
we use great plainness of speech and not
as Moses which put a veil over his face
that the children of Israel could not
steadfastly look to the end of that
which is
abolished but their minds were blind for
until this day remaineth the same Veil
un taken away in the reading of the Old
Testament which Veil is done away in
Christ but even
until I'm we're not going to read all
this what these people are saying is
that that the the new that Paul's
writing and the writing in the New
Testament overrides the writing of the
Old Testament so the question here is
why should uh I have to wait CU it going
to take far right here until till I get
circumcised to get baptized Paul cannot
override god so let's go into Genesis
the 17th chapter but we're going to do
some quick reading here I have several
scriptures that did this on this because
people are
listening and they need to know better
Genesis 17 we going to read from 9 to 14
real
quick and God said unto Abraham thou
shall keep my Covenant therefore thou
and thy seed after thee and
generation this is my Covenant which ye
shall keep between me and you and thy
seed after thee every man child among
you shall be circumcised and you shall
circumcise the Flesh of your forkin and
it shall be a token of the Covenant
between me and you and he that is eight
days old shall be circumcised among you
every man child in your generation he
that is born in the house or bought with
money of any stranger which is not of
thy seed he that is born in thy house
and he that is bought with th money must
needs be circumcised my Covenant shall
be in your flesh for an Everlasting
Covenant and the uncircumcised Man Child
whose flesh have is foreskin is not
circumcised that Soul shall be cut off
from his people he have broken my
Covenant and you know what cut off mean
that's thrown in the Lake of Fire now
God told this to Abraham Abraham didn't
tell it to God this is not Moses law
either this is the law of God so any
uncircumcised male whether he's a
stranger or whether he's bought with
money that mean that represent being
bought with the blood of Jesus if he is
not circumcised he going to be cut off
from among his brothers now let's go to
Exodus the 12th chapter right
quick and we're going to read 43 and
44 then we're going to skip down and
read 48 and
49 read it when you get there and the
Lord said unto Moses and Aaron this is
the ordinance of the Passover there
shall No Stranger eat thereof but every
man Serv that is bought for money when
thou H has circumcised him then shall he
eat
thereof that's the ordinance of the pan
over no stranger eat there but if he
going but if he will eat he got to be
circumcised cu no circumcised male shall
eat thereof go ahead a foreigner and a
highest servant shall not eat
thereof skip down to 48 48 go ahead and
when a stranger shall sour with thee and
will keep the Passover to the Lord that
all his males be circumcised and then
let them come near and keep it and he
shall be as one that is born in the land
but no uncircumcised person shall eat
thereof one law shall be to him that is
homeborn and unto the stranger that
sourth for
monkey now that's the pant over what did
the pant over who did the pant over
represent represent let me let me show
you who they
represent let go because if you're not
uncircumcised uh uh you can go to First
Corinthians 5 and 7 but if you're not
uncircumcised you can't even partake in
a Passover right that's who what it
represent First Corinthians 5 and
7 Purge out therefore the old Le that ye
may be a new love as ye are unleavened
for even Christ Our Passover is
sacrifice for us
so let's let you know you can't even in
order for you to take part in in Christ
you got to be baptized it tell you in
galatian the 3 chapter all those that
baptized in Christ have put on Christ
that's right you neither Jew Gentile
nether na not free you children of God
the children of Abraham and have
according to the promise so now you
can't take part of him now when the Lord
come
back and set his kingdom upon this Earth
let's see what he said concerning
circumcision uh uh uh let's go into
Ezekiel the 44th
chapter we're going to read 6 and seven
and Skip down to verse
n and thou shall say to the rebellious
even to the house of Israel thus sayith
the Lord God oh ye House of Israel let
it suffice you of all your Abomination
and that ye have bought Into My
Sanctuary strangers uncircumcised
what he call this Abomination didn't it
that's right let it you of all your
Abomination and that you have brought
into My Sanctuary who read it again that
ye have brought in My Sanctuary
strangers uncircumcised in heart and
uncircumcised flesh to be in My
Sanctuary hold on people read and said
well you don't have to be circumcised In
the Flesh now all you got to do is be
circumcised in the heart the Lord e the
Lord just covered both of that didn't
he as uncircumcised In the Flesh not in
the heart finish that to be in My
Sanctuary to pollute it even my house
when you offer my bread the fat and the
blood and they have broken my Covenant
because of all your
Abominations is now you going to bring
them in uncircumcised people and they
going to he brought them in that done
through the years I'm pretty sure they
St after Paul didn't come up with that
and said you have polluted my house and
they have broken my Covenant because of
your
Abomination down to verse n what he said
concerning uncircumcised stranger go
ahead thus say the Lord God no stranger
uncircumcised and high nor uncircumcised
in flesh shall enter into my sanctuary
of any stranger that is among the
children of
Israel no because never was a flight
over Israel it was always a flight over
the
stranger but he said
No No Stranger is going to come into my
Sanctuary that's why the Lord setting up
but it was never a fight about Israel uh
Israel in the first place was always the
stranger the Gentiles of a stranger and
a situation come up when
Paul circumcised somebody let's go into
First Corinthians the 16th chapter and
read verses 1 through3
1 Corinthians
right now concerning the collection for
the Saints as I have given order to the
Church of gal galatia even so do ye upon
the
first this is this is acts I'm sorry
acts 16
1-3 my mistake
there came he to Derby debris to Derby
and Lyra and behold a certain disciple
was there named timas the son of a
certain woman which was a Jewish and
believed but his father was a Greek
which was well reported of by the
Brethren that were eler and Iconium and
him will Paul have to go forth with them
and took and circumcised him because of
the Jews which were in those quarters
for they knew all that his father was a
Greek now so why is that Paul
circumcised
Timothy because he had a Hebrew
mother so now that was uh uh that's
concerning the stranger always
concerning the stranger but as far as
Israel is concerned
nobody escap escaped the circumcision
that God gave to Abraham and if he did
there are consequences let's go into
Exodus the 4th
chapter and we going to read verses 19
and 20 and we're going to skip down and
read verses 24-
26 so this is a serious matter
4:19 and
20 then
24 go ahead and the Lord said unto Moses
and Moses and Midian go return unto
Egypt for all the men are dead which
sought th life and Moses took his wife
and his son and set them upon an ass and
he returned to the land of Egypt and
Moses took the rod of God in his
hand so now Moses going to bring Israel
out of Egypt God God sent him there and
gave him a rod that Rod had a lot of
power in it God put rod in so he took
his wife and his and his kids and and
his Rod a God and he went back to Egypt
let's see what happened what what
happened on their way there was that the
20th verse
yeah down to verse
24 and it came to pass by the way in the
end that the Lord met him and sought to
kill him then theor took wait a minute
the Lord me but wasn't he was going to
kill
Moses
y Moses is a prototype of God but why is
that go ahead and read then seor took a
Shar Stone and cut off the foreskin of
her son and cast it at his feet and said
surely a bloody husband are thou to
me Moses forgot to circumcise his son
his wife took a sharp Stone and
circumcised and threw the skin at Moses
feet and what happened so he let him go
then she said a bloody husband Thou Art
because of the
circumcision look God was going to kill
mes because he forgot to circumcise his
son this is Moses the Prototype of
Jesus
now Peter gave some good advice and I
and uh you don't have to take it but you
ain't got to worry about it at the
Israel of
God it is what it is but let's look at
Peter's uh uh uh advice let's go into
second
Peter first
chapter we going to read verse 16 then
we're going to skip down and read uh uh
verse 19 to
21 but we have for we have not followed
cunning devis favors
when we made known unto you the power
and coming of our Lord Jesus Christ but
were eyewitnesses of his majesty now
this is Peter letting the people know
look we didn't we haven't made no kind
stories we was eyewitness with Jesus we
we was there when he did all the
Miracles we was there when he heard the
father talk to him from heaven we was
there
but we going to give you something
that's even more better than our word
excuse now to verse 19 and read the
21 we have also a more sure word of
Prophecy where un until ye do well that
you take heed as unto a light that
shineth in the dark place until the day
Dawn and the day star arise in your
hearts knowing this first that no
Prophecy of the scripture is of any
private
interpretation for the prophecy came not
in Old Time by the will of man but holy
men of God spake as they were moved by
the Holy
Ghost now Peter said we have a most sure
word of Prophecy when you go in the New
Testament it seem like it's
contradicting go back and see what
prophecy said and prophecy speaks
plain and the reason that uh uh people
of understanding don't baptize
uncircumcised men it's just like praying
over a dead C God said you going to cut
off be cut off from among you people and
you get cut off brother that mean you're
going to the Lor fire yep right that's
all I have to
say hey can we just read that one verse
in Luke uh two Luke 2 and one verse
verse 21 Luke 2 and
21 what does it say
read luk two and
verse is this the one here that was
gonna kill Moses for not circumcising
his kid go ahead brother and when it was
eight days were accomplished for the
circumcision of the child his name was
called Jesus which was so named of the
Angels before he was conceived in the
womb so Jesus had circumcised didn't sir
so now who you goingon to listen to God
Jesus uh
Paul listen to
Jesus I know who we going to listen to
but you make the choice whoever this
brother that asked this question
that's
all thank you for that and we hope that
that answered your question as we move
on to our next question moving on Jun
North for asks what is Paul saying in
second Corinthians 3 vers
12-8 all
right might have to kind of see what the
guest call the weigh in on this one too
uh let's go to 2 Corinthians 3 and open
to the pan also 2
Corinthians the 3
chapter and they want verse
12-8 and just be expounding on a little
bit about what's being said here second
up brother cor picked that up at verse
11 okay second Corinthians
3 and pick it up at at verse
11 okay
for that which is done away was glorious
much more that which remaineth is
glorious seeing then that we have such
hope we use great plainness of speech
and not as Moses which put a veil over
his face that the children of Israel
could not steadfastly look to the end of
that which is abolished but their minds
were for until this dayth the same Veil
untaken away in the reading of the Old
Testament which Veil is done away in
Christ but even until this day when
Moses is read the veil is upon their
hearts nevertheless when it shall turn
to the Lord the veil shall be taken away
now the Lord is that spirit and where
the spirit of the Lord is there is
Liberty there's
freedom but we all with open face behold
of eyes in the glass the glory of the
Lord are changed into the same image
from glory to glory even as by the
spirit of the Lord
yes so open to the panel somebody want
to exp all Paul all Paul is saying is
that the the plan of God was Paul is
explaining to the Corinthians the plan
of God is to graduate this man from
flesh to Spirit and a lot of people
didn't understand that so they was
blinded they were spiritually blinded
with that build which represented that
spiritual blindness and even to this day
the people don't understand that God is
creating God so therefore the people
don't understand that so that b is still
over they over they hearts or their
minds today they don't understand that
God is creating God
right yeah I like hear that verse 13 how
say Moses started to he started to Glow
he was taking on the characteristics of
God just by being around that's right
the end of man is God and whatever be in
the Lake of Fire
yeah all about making us in him in his
image there you go
yeah all
right we'll leave it there and we'll
move on to our next question
sister yes 32 DBS ask which King James
Bible version do you use and why example
161 King James new King James version
modern King James version authorized
version King James Bible
Etc Bo they got a lot of King James
Bibles and other Bibles on the planet
Julius what you say there's only one
version of the English Bible That's the
King James there are many translations
of that version we use at the Israel of
God we use the King James version of the
161 which is also the same as the
authorized version we use it for it
accuracy we use it for the the prophecy
we understand it is the word of God it
is the mind of God and we know that in
this book he warns us not to add nor
take away in Deuteronomy or at the end
of Revelation don't take away from
anything because it is the mind of God
King James did not write a word of it
all he did was give permission for it to
be translated from the Greek Hebrew
Aramaic and Latin into the king's
language which was at that time English
the English that they spoke so we used
the 1611 it's written in our language we
can understand and it teaches us where
man came from and how God is GNA make
man God so now let's go to a place right
here let's go to Isaiah the 8th chapter
and this what I love about it it's plain
it's understandable and there are 8,000
changes in the new King James what's
wrong with the uh authorized
version Isaiah
8 Isaiah 8 read verse 16 and then read
verse
21 bind up the testimony seal the law
among my
disciples verse 20 uhuh to the law and
to the testimony if they speak not
according to this word it is because
there is no light in them they don't
have no understanding if they don't
understand this if they speak not
according to this they don't have no
understanding let's go to Second Peter 1
and I'm going to piggy back out what the
guest colist uh h said it because we get
this question a
lot all these Bibles translation they
all start with in the beginning God but
then they go from there they go off into
everything else SE tuent and whatsoever
second Peter 1 second Peter 1 begin
reading at verse 15 and 16
tzel more I will endeavor that ye may be
able after my decease to have these
things always in
remembrance for we have not follow H
device favor when we may known unto you
the power and coming of our Lord Jesus
Christ but were eyewitnesses of his
majesty but eyewitnesses of his majesty
right skip down to verse 19 and we going
19 to 21 what we just read here on the
statement that was made a few minutes
ago this right here is what captures me
right here go ahead we have also a moral
word of Prophecy the Bible is a book of
Prophecy it's a book of prayer it tells
how you what man came from and where man
is going go ahead where unto ye do well
that ye take heed as into a light that
shineth in the dark BLS until the day
Dawn and the day star arise in your
hearts that day Dawn and the day star is
the understanding of the word of God in
your mind go ahead brother verse 20
knowing this first that no Prophecy of
the scripture is of any private
interpretation uhhuh for the prophecy
came not in Old Time by the will of man
but ho holy men of God spake as they
were moved by the Holy Ghost and that is
the key right there holy men of God
that's why it's called the Holy Bible
because the holy men of God spake as
they were moved by the Holy Ghost
beginning from Moses to John so
therefore hey we got everything that we
need to get salvation sisters and
brothers so all these other versions
they come and they could make all kind
of changes and that is designed by Satan
devil to get you cut
off anybody else want to
add yeah brother Julius and we use the
King James Bible because that Bible
matches up the best with history out of
all the Bibles on the planet and that
Bible tells you that you must need be
circumcised right yeah all right so we
hope that answered your question as we
keep on moving keep moving Harold
Ferguson as for explanation on First
Peter 3 vers 18- 20 who was he preaching
to and what was being preached to
them all right 1 Peter 3:18 through2
let's go there
tanzel and when you get there go ahead
and the guest caller will share some
light on who was he preaching to and
what was being preached to
them well Christ also have one suffer
for sins the just for the unjust that he
might bring us to God being put to death
in the flass but quickness by the Spirit
by which also he went and preaching into
the spirit in prison which sometimes
were disobedient when Once the long
suffering of God waited for in the days
of Noah while the ark was up preparing
wherein few that is eight Souls were
saved by water
now people read this they try to say
when Jesus
died when he went to when he went the
grave he went in the grave and he
preached to the Dead uh uh uh people
when he said preach to the spirit in in
prison first thing is we got to find
out we got to find out uh
uh what the spirit is and what and and
uh uh and then we'll know what time it
was but let's go and read he said he
preach to the spirit and prison during
the what did he said during the time of
job didn't he say that correct Noah yeah
Noah Noah no of Noah right put the death
put the death in the flesh but uh uh
quicker in the spirit now all the say
and that same spirit that body he had
was the form he used when he uh uh uh uh
was there in the days of Noah now let's
go and look at something first thing we
want to find out is uh uh
uh who was prison and what was they
let's go into
Jude the first chapter and read verse 5
and
six right the book of
[Music]
Jude little book right before
Revelations
okay I will
there vers 5 and
six
okay I will therefore put you in
remembrance though ye once knew this how
that the Lord having saved the people
out of the land of Egypt afterward
destroyed them that believed not and the
angels which kept not their first estate
but at their own inhabitations he have
reserved in Everlasting chains under
Darkness unto the Judgment of the great
day do not they're in prison right now
on the chains of Darkness they can't
appear in front of nobody these angels
now what are these angels let's go into
Hebrews the first chapter and read verse
7 Hebrews 1 and
seven and of the angels He said who
maketh his Angel spirit and his
ministers a flame of fire now he make
his angels Spirits through angels of
spirits through the angels that are in
spir in prison right now under Darkness
chains of Darkness are angels so they
are spirit so what is man let's go into
Genesis the uh 2 chapter and read verse
Genesis 2
and7
right read it and the Lord God formed
man of the Dust of the ground and
breathe to his noals the breath of life
and Man became a living
Soul so now man is a soul angels of
spirits now Jesus he he preached to the
spirit
that uh that was in prison during the
times of Noah let's go to one more place
let's go to First Corinthians 15th
chapter and we going to read verses 45
to
47 no 45 rather and yeah 47 go ahead and
read and so
it the first man Adam was made a living
soul and the last Adam was made a
Quicken the spirit how be it th was not
first which is spiritual but that which
is natural and afterward
that which is spiritual the first man is
of the earth Earthly the second man is
the Lord From
Heaven yes now so now man is a is is a
soul and Jesus is the spirit like all
the Angels so when Jesus died was
crucified and killed in the flesh when
he rose he was a spirit being and he was
the same type being that he was in the
days of Noah when he had to preach to
them angels that he have on the chains
of Darkness though Jesus didn't preach
to no dead people in the grave he
preached to them angels in the days of
Noah while Noah was building an ark CU
obvious they was restless and they
wanted to get out this new
world so
now he was talking to
Angels don't have to say all right hope
that answered your question there sister
Deborah as we keep
rolling ah yes Ben F says I'm having
trouble
distinguishing who is who can you help
me understand who is being referenced in
Hosea chapter 5 they reference Ephraim
Israel and Judah verse five is a good e
example all right Hosea chapter 5 Shar
some light brother Jerome
let's go to that Hosea 5 and5 T when you
get it go ahead and read and the pride
of Israel doeth testify to his face
therefore shall Israel and Ephraim fall
in their iniquities Judah also shall
fall with
them okay this is referring to uh when
you see Ephraim right here that's
actually referring to the the nine
tribes and Ephraim was set over the nine
tribes the tribe of Ephraim was set over
and Judah when you see Judah here that's
talking about three tribes and the three
tribes were um Benjamin Levi and Judah
okay so let's let's go to um
Ezra chapter
one read verse two and Skip to verse
five
okay yeah this is when uh
um um the three tribes that's under the
banner of
Judah was going to come back home and U
rebuild the Temple in
Jerusalem we at Ezra uh two first
chapter the first chapter first chapter
yeah read verse two and Skip to verse
five then says Cyrus King of Persia Lord
God Of Heaven have given me all the
kingdoms of the earth and he have
charged me to build him an house at
Jerusalem which is in Judea
yeah skip to verse five yeah then rose
up the chief of the fathers of Judah and
Benjamin and the priests and the Levites
with all them who Spirit God had raised
to go up to build the house of the Lord
which is in Jerusalem and those are the
three tribes that was uh in Jerusalem
even when Jesus came in the flesh was on
the scene and these three were normally
referred to as Jews but just like Paul
said you know I'm a benjamite but he's
under the banner of Judah because those
three tribes they were referred to as
Jews okay right um let's go to uh
Ezekiel chapter
37 talking about the two sticks that the
Lord is uh going to bring back together
and make them one nation again CU right
now you got what be referred ref to as
two Nations even though we know it's one
you know nine tribes was referred to as
one nation and three tribes referred to
another Nation I'm G put them back
together okay when he return uh Ezekiel
37 read verse 15 and 16 and then we
gonna
skip the word of the Lord came again
unto me saying moreover thou son of man
take the one stick and write it upon it
for Judah and for the children of Israel
his companions his companions were the
were the other two tribes that we read
Benjamin and Levi go ahead then take
another stick and write upon it for
Joseph The Stick of Ephraim and for all
the house of Israel his companions
Ephraim was the head tribe of the nine
his companions go
ahead and join one to another into one
stick and they shall become one in thy
hand okay skip down to verse 21 read to
the
22 and say unto them thus sayth the Lord
God behold I will take the children of
Israel from among the heathens whether
they be gone and will gather them on
every side and bring them into their own
land and I will make them one nation in
the land upon the mountains of Israel
and one King shall be king to them all
and they shall be no more two Nations
heither shall there be divided into two
kingdoms anymore at all yeah that's all
I got on
here EXC all right thank you for that
there brother when the Lord put the
nation back together again all right
sister Deborah we're moving
on yes All Day production says in
Matthew 24 verse2 when it's time to flee
are we all going to flee to the
Wilderness and at the same time seem
like the winter or the Sabbath day is
two different time
periods all right so when it's time to
flee let's go to Matthew
24 24 and let's pick it up at that verse
uh 15 and read down because there's a
reason you have to flee go ahead tanel
and when ye therefore shall see the
abomination of desolation spoken of by
Daniel the Prophet stand in the Holy
Place whoo reth let them understand yeah
go ahead then let them which be Jud flee
to the
mountains let him which is on the
housetop not come down to take anything
out of his
house neither let him which is in the
field return back to take his
clothes and woe unto them that which are
with child and to them that give suck in
those days but pray ye that your flight
be not in the winter neither on the
Sabbath day so you pray that your flight
don't be in the winter or on the Sabbath
day because in the winter time sometimes
it's tough to fly flights get cancelled
um things of that nature and on the
Sabbath day over there in the land
things shut down so it can make it
tougher for
you go ahead read brother but then shall
be Great Tribulation such as were not
since the beginning of the world to this
time
no nor ever shall be all right going to
be a terrible time open to the panel in
regards to that
question well the qu well the answer is
yes everybody should free at the same
time yep because when you see
Abomination stand in the Holy place is
when you see the pope go into the temple
that's going to be built you ain't got a
whole lot of time that's why I said if
you're on the housetop don't come down
if you're on the in the field don't come
back to your house
you better flee to the Wilderness as
soon as you can in the Sabbath day and
winter are not two different times those
are times of the year Sabbath day is the
seventh day of the week and winter is in
the winter time they got nothing to do
with the time that's all I have to say
all right hope that ansed your question
as we move
on yes TJ says I'm 31 and ready to get
married but not sure what I'm supposed
to set up before doing it are there
scriptures that tell me what to do
first all right let's open that up to
the panel he say um I'm supposed he
doesn't really know and what is is he
supposed to set up um supposed to make
sure you're ready to take on a wife and
open to the panel
baby could you repeat the question
please yes I'm 31 and ready to get
married but not sure what I'm supposed
to set up before doing it are there
scriptures that tell me what to do
first the book tell you to avoid
fornication let every man have his own
wife let let every woman have her own
husband and make sure that you ready
according to the word of God you know
pray to the Lord keep his Commandments
here lead and guide you into all truth
right don't be unequally yolked don't be
unequally Yol that's for
sure
Y and
um so many other things you'll get if
you somebody at the Israel of God do
your wedding for you get some other tips
on what you're supposed to do after you
become married so you know love your
wife like Christ loved the church and
the wife's supposed to make sure she
give her husband you know much respect
and so love is supposed to be flowing
through anybody
else all right we're gonna leave it
right there and move on to our next
question I believe now we getting ready
to journey into new territory
yes we are now into tonight's Q&A for
Wednesday September the 18
2024 sister Tanisha says or ask if you
have your own business although we don't
celebrate none of the pagan holidays can
you have a promotion for them days being
most of the world shops heavily for them
days or will I be in
violation yes caller can you share some
light on um this day that they question
about yeah let's go into Matthews 6
chapter and read verse
24 Matthew
6 and verse
24 okay verse
2 no man can ser two masters either he
will hate the one and love the other or
else he will hold to the one and despise
the other you cannot serve god in
me so you cannot promote
paganism and the word of
God that's all I have to say all right
sister Deborah our next question next
question TX Domino says I was told that
John the Baptist was the last prophet or
maybe I misheard if so acts 13 verse 1
and 1 corini 12 verse 30 verse
28 says different or maybe I'm reading
that
incorrectly is this
true all right call share
some the Lord tell you to get wisdom and
but with all you getting get
understanding now let let's dissect this
little uh uh let's go and read this
these uh uh what it says here what it
say acts what 13 verse
one read it
first now therefore now there were in
the church that was at Antioch certain
prophets and teaches as Barnabas and
Simeon that was called Niger and Lucius
of sirene and many
Manan which had been brought up with
Herod the the T and
Saul okay so we had a guy there they
call the prophet right now let's go into
First Corinthians read 12 and
26 what was that 1 Corinthians 12 and
26 uh 12 and
28 and God have said some of the church
first apostles secondarily prophet
thoroughly teaches after that Miracles
then Gifts of healings helps government
diversities of
tongues now it speaks of prophets D
don't it but let's go and see what Jesus
said I Think Jesus would outweighs
everybody so let's go to
Matthew and read verses
11-13 what was that Cornel
Matthew Matthew the 10th chapter
verses
11-13
right Matthew
11 and unto whosoever city or town you
shall enter inquire who and it is worthy
and there abide till you go then
and wait you you read Matthew the 10th
chapter
yeah and verse 11
yeah so they're speaking about John the
Baptist it the 11th
chapter I'm telling uh
uh may let me see read a little more
let's see what it said when when you
know when Jesus was talking about John
the Baptist that there ain't none
greater among women than John the
Matthew
oh Matthews 11 well I put the wrong one
down there and start at verse 11 and see
what it
say verily I say unto you among them
that are born of women there have not
risen a greater than John the Baptist
notwithstanding he that is least in the
Kingdom of Heaven is greater than he go
ahead and from the days of John the
Baptist until now the Kingdom of Heaven
suffer violence and the violent taketh
it by force for all the prophets and the
law prophesies until
John and see what it said for all the
and the law prophesies unto John did you
finish that that's
it so so that's that's where it stops
said read that verse
again for all the prophets in the law
prophesy unto
John now I let you know and John when he
got to John there was the end of it
that's all the prophets from Genesis to
uh uh
uh uh uh Malachi and the
last so now any other person that's a
prophet they will not prophesy anything
that was not
written
right the reason I know because this is
what the Lord said about it go to
Revelation the 22nd chapter verse 18 and
for I testified unto every man that hear
the words of the prophecy of this book
If any man shall add unto these things
God shall add unto him the plagues that
are written in this book and if any man
shall take away from the words of the
book of of the book of this prophecy God
shall take away his part out of the book
of life and out of the holy city and
from the things which are written in
this book
look do not if you got some prophets
they are secondhand prophets because
they prophesying whatever already been
prophesied because Solomon tell you they
ain't nothing new Under the Sun right
that's like said all of the
prophets prophesied unto
John John was the last of it because he
the one that brought put something new
on the table what was that to
baptism what you have to do if you going
to be in Christ you got to be baptized
if you're going to get under the New
Covenant so he brought something that
wasn't even there and hadn't been done
before like Jesus said all the
prophets and prophecy prophesied unto
John John was the last prophet that is
right else was second
hand right yeah best we can do brother
Cornel is come in the spirit of the
prophets we cannot add or take away from
the book that's right that's right yep
yep John was a like he say was the last
prophet he the one that baptized Jesus
that's right sir so all right hope that
anwers your question there as we move on
moving on DD says my fiance say that he
doesn't need my consent to have
relations with me because my body body
belongs to him what if I'm sick or
having pain Etc I still have to let him
do it I say no and he doesn't and he
does it anyway isn't that a
salt yes I I have something that the
Lord wrote about uh guys like
Fon let's go into Malachi the second
chapter
Malachi
2 uhuh start at verse
13 and this have ye
done
malach yeah and this have ye done again
covering the alt of the Lord with tears
with weeping and with crying out in so
much that he regardeth not the offering
anymore or receive it with Good Will at
your
hand go ahead yet ye say wherefore
because the Lord have been witnessed
between thee and the wife of thy youth
against whom thou
treacherously yet is she thy companion
and the wife of thy
Covenant go ahead not she but she said
fiance she didn't say nothing but wife
did
she oh
okay but I'm I'm going show you what he
said by the wife finish this
verse and did not he make one yet have
he the residue of the spirit and with
wherefore one that he might seek a Godly
SE therefore take heed to your spirit
and let none deal treacherously against
the wife is
you right God Is Watching Over the wife
over the married people and he's saying
that the ones that uh this this brother
the man is married to this woman he be
praying because and the Lord ain't
asking his prayer he because he been
witness between him and the wife of his
youth he saiding don't deal
treacherously with the wife of his youth
right it's all that simple do now but
they ain't even married you talking
about
fiance how is it
that you are married or not married this
guy own you when somebody go back to
First Corinthians 7th chapter and and
see what the Lord said about
fornication First Corinthians the seven
chapter uhuh pick it up at verse
one you you can start
there now concerning the things where of
ye wrote unto me it is good for a man
not to touch a woman nevertheless to to
avoid fornication that every man have
his own wife and that every woman have
her own husband do now to avoid
fornication you're supposed to get
married now what's going to happen to
fornicators let's skip down where the
Lord say it's better to
marry verse
n okay but if they cannot but if they
cannot contain if they cannot
let them marry for it is better to marry
than to
burn do not if you uh your Beyonce is is
is forcing
you you already commit an adultery but
also according to man's law he is raping
you but if but even if you should get
married to this
guy he don't belong to you he don't own
you you have to make your own decision
and if you make the wrong decision
because of him you following him let me
show you what can happen to
you that's if you're
married acts the 5th
chapter we're going to start reading
that verse one acts 5 and
one but a certain man named inan with
Safari his wife sold a possession and
kept back part of the price his wife
also also been privy to it and brought a
certain part and laid it at the apostles
feet but Peter said andah why have Satan
F thy heart to Li of the Holy Ghost and
to keep back part of the price of the
land
while and those days they had pledge
that they were going to sell proper and
they going to give all of the money to
the church but this man here he got
slick and decided I'm going to sell the
property but I'm going to give a little
of it a part of it but that was the part
of the uh plag he was supposed to give
all of it so now when he come and gave
part of it then what did Peter say go
ahead while it remaining was it not thy
own and after it was so was it not in
thy own power why H has thou conceived
this thing in thy heart thou has not
lied unto men but unto
God
and unto God go ahead and ananas hearing
these words fell down and gave up the
ghost and great fear came on all them
that heard these
things uhhuh and the young men
arose listen to me this man
lied to the Holy Ghost to the Lord and
God killed him now let's see what's
going to happen to the woman and first
the young man took him out verse six and
go ahead and the young men arose wound
them up carried them out and buried them
and it was a about the space of three
hours after when his wife not knowing
what was done came in and Peter answered
unto her tell me whether you sold the
land for so much and she said yeah for
so much then Peter said unto her now
Peter asked
her you know in other words uh uh
uh do you know do you know what he sold
his land for for so she said yeah so she
sided with him go ahead
then Peter said unto her how is it that
ye have agreed together to tempt the
spirit of the Lord behold the feet of
them which have buried thy husband are
at the door and shall carry thee
out then fell she down straight way at
his feet and yielded up The Ghost and
the young man came in and found her dead
and carrying her forth buried her by her
husband do now
if he owned
her then the Lord wouldn't have killed
her because she wouldn't have had a
choice but she had a choice each
individual have a choice it is written
you have to work out your own salvation
with fear and trembling this man don't
own you first thing is he haven't even
legally married you so your fance and
you sing him then both of you are
fornicators want some good
advice stop committing fornication and
get married but with this kind of
mindset then maybe you should think
about it you might be
becoming unequally yolked for anybody
that think you own you that's all I have
to
say all right there was some wise light
there hope that answered your question
as we continue to move on to our next
yes Israelites by Blood Brandon says I'm
ready to be baptized will iog come to
Iowa to baptize
me sure our job is to baptize all those
that have repented and coming to the
knowledge of God when it's their hard
desire guess
caller no J not gonna come there to
baptize you you want to get baptized
then you get to the I and we will
baptize
you oh okay we don't have a place in
our all
right go on the internet and find out
the one that's closest to
you and call the number and set up a
date if you have been
circumcised yes first that that comes
before the
baptism
y all right hope that answered your
question there sister Deborah we know
how time flies when you're having
fun yes so Zion says if no one has ever
heard the father's voice at any time
whose voice did the people hear in John
12 verse
28 John 12 and
28 well you can rest assured no one has
heard the father's voice at any time so
keep that in your mind that that Reigns
true but let's open this up to the panel
after we go to that John 12 and verse
28 because that is absolutely true no
one has ever heard the father's Voice or
seen his shape at any time at anytime
brother John 12 and 28 first there
brother
tanzel all
right father glorify thy name then came
there a voice from Heaven saying I have
both glorified it and will glorified it
again all right now turn back to John
five John
five and let's pick it up at that verse
John
537 yes sir and the father himself which
sent me have borne witness of me ye have
neither heard his voice at any time nor
seen his
shape anybody else on the panel John
5339 John 539 search the scripture for
in them ye think ye have eternal life
and they are
which testify me verse
46 for ye believe Moses you would have
believed me for he wrote of
me
but but if you believe not his writing
how should ye believe my
words so that was now let me let me go
and show you who what voice he heard
let's go into Genesis the 22nd chapter
yes sir
read verses 1 and two and Skip down to
verse 9 and
continue and it came to pass after these
things that God T did temp Abraham and
said unto him Abraham and he said behold
here am I and he said take now thy son
thy only son Isaac whom thou lovest and
get thee into the land of Mariah and
offer him therefore a burnt offering
upon one of the mountain which I will
tell
thee now now who was talking here and
said you know and it came to pass that
God tempt
Abraham and said unto him
Abraham so this is look like it's God's
talking right skip let's keep
reading did you say skip down to verse
n and then and they came to the place
which God had told him of and Abraham
built an altar there laid the wood in
order and bound Isaac his son and laid
him on the altar upon the wood Abraham
stretched forth his hand and took the
knife to slay his son and the angel of
the Lord called unto him out of heaven
and said Abraham
Abraham and he said here am I and he
said lay not thy hand upon the L neither
do thou anything unto him for now I know
that thou fearest God seeing thou H has
not withheld thy son thy only son from
me so there was an angel that said that
right skip down to verse
15 and the angel of the Lord called unto
Abraham Out of Heaven the second time
and he said by myself have I sworn
sayeth the Lord for because thou has
done this thing and has not withheld thy
son thy only son that in blessings I
Will Bless thee and in multiplying I
will multiply thy seed as the stars of
the heaven and as
the that's enough the voice that he
heard was an angel voice
right don't have to say all right and
sister Deborah I believe that is a good
question to end tonight's session on
time check yes the time is
9:01 all right we' like to thank
everybody from all around the world who
tuned in with us to ask your questions
and we Jo and answer them and we want to
say if you submitted a question we
didn't have an opportunity to get to it
this evening don't resubmit it sister
Deborah take it put it in rotation and
we will deal with that question next
week so thank you all again and until we
all come together again let us all be
safe and be blessed and may the Lord
have mercy on us all is brother CH
closes us
up Our Father which are in heaven
Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom come
that will be done in earth as it is in
heaven give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us of our debts as we
forgive our debt to us and lead us not
into temptation but Deliver Us from Evil
thine is the kingdom and the power and
the glory forever in Jesus name we pray
amen